# Seira Yasumatsu

Creative problem solver and goal oriented product designer who identifies the right problem to solve and thrives to provide design experiences with empathy for the real users.

#### CONTACT

415.606.2993

≤ seiray117@gmail.com

SanFrancisco, CA

seirayasumatsu.com

in linkedin

github.com

# **SKILLS**

Visual Design
UX/UI Design
User Research & Testing
Personas & User Stories
Brand Strategy & Identity
Information Architecture
Wireframes
Prototyping & Usability Testing

#### **TOOLS**

Adobe Creative Suite
Figma
InVision
Maze
HTML, CSS, & JavaScript
GitHub
Balsamiq
SolidWorks & Rhino3D

# **AWARDS**

## **Sodexo Scholarship**

San Francisco State University November 2017

## **Stanford Design Challenge**

Stanford Center of Longevity April 2018

## **PROJECTS**

behub | iOS Prototype and Marketing Site

behub

Designed to help users to manage and organize a family's schedule and content by collaborating among family members. Used Invision and Maze for user research and testing and Figma for prototyping.

STEMA | Web Prototype and wearable device prototype

**STEMA** 

Designed a platform for educators, parents, and girls to create a STEM community with wearable devices. Web Prototype created with Adobe XD and Adobe Creative Suite.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bloc** | 2018-2019

User Experience & Front End Development Apprenticeship

San Francisco State University | Class of 2018

BS in Industrial Design

**Diablo Valley College** | Class of 2012

AS in Early Childhood Education

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Bloc

UX Design & Front End Development Apprenticeship I Oct. 2018—June 2019

- Designed and developed iOS and web prototype using Figma and Adobe Suite
- Conducted user-surveys with 40 potential users and performed survey analysis
- Created a design style guide that was used across multi-platforms
- Packaged deliverables to hand off to an engineering team
- Developed a responsive and intuitive website by using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

# Stanford Center of Longevity Design Challenge

UX/Product Design I Sep. 2017—Apr. 2018

- Designed and developed a versatile garden station following the design process
- Iterated the design based on user research, user feedback, and user testing
- Designed and delivered visual and graphical presentations for over 100 people

# **Growing Light Montessori School**

Early Childhood Educator & Creative Director I Mar. 2010—May 2014

- Implemented activities, toys, and materials based on children's interest and needs
- Planned and introduced a better design system for the afternoon-care transition